Burd-Shippen Papers 1708-1792 Mss.B.B892
American Philosophical Society
- Military, 1748 - 1772, undated; Series III
  - Account with William Smith..., 1759 June - 1760 February; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 7)
    Relates to account for Burd to collect debts owed Smith.
  - Account against various soldiers ..., 1759 July; 1p.; Jameson, David (Box 7)
    Lists names of soldiers who owe him money and amount.
  - Authorization to James Burd to receive his pay..., 1759 July 8; 1p.; Ramsay, John (Box 7)
    Authorization while serving the battalion.
  - Report of the sick ..., 1759 July 16; 1p.; Morgan, John (Box 7)
    List of men sick by name.
  - Report of the men who are unable to march, 1759 July 22; 1p. (Box 7)
    List of men by name and reason.
  - Certification that Valentine Harman is a recruit, 1759 August 3; 1p.; Armstrong, G. (Box 7)
    Certifies Harman is a recruit and the company he serves with.
  - Return of provisions in store at Guests' place ..., 1759 September 14; 1p. (Box 7)
    Return for beef and flour.
  - Return for shoes and nails..., 1759 September 18; 1p.; Price, John (Box 7)
    List of material needed to finish shoeing four teams of horses. Gives wagoners' names.
  - Account of horses delivered the wagoners..., 1759 September 19; 1p. (Box 7)
    Lists wagoners names, and number of horses given.
  - A list of carpenter's tools wanting at the works ... Monongahela, 1759 September 30; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 7)
    Lists tools and number needed.
  - List of carpenter's tools wanting..., 1759 September 30; 1p. (Box 7)
    List of tools and number needed (identical to list above).
  - Account of James Burd for his company [fragment], 1759; 1p. (Box 7)
    Lists items delivered to companies.
  - Col. James Burd's account for various members of his company, 1759; 1p. (Box 6, Box 7)
    Accounting of money owed by men in his company.
  - Recruiting account [of James Burd?] for William Mackrel., 1759; 1p. (Box 7)
    Money paid for recruiting.
  - Roll Penn. Regt. Hon. William Denny, Colonel in Chief, 1759; 10pp. (Box 7)
    Gives the list of officers in the Three Battalions of the Pennsylvania Regiment, including date of commission.
  - Returns of Forage, 1759; 1p. (Box 7)
    Lists number of officers and men at certain locations.
  - Statement of various men paid..., 1759; 1p. (Box 7)
    Lists name and rank of men, with amount paid.
  - Certification that he paid James Burd., 1760 January 28; 1p.; Young James (Box 7)
    Certification of pay for Isaac Miller.
  - Account with Colonel Shippen, 1760 February 20; 1p.; Lenhere, Philip (Box 7)
    Items purchased and amount.
  - Statement of accounts with James Burd..., 1760 March 27; 1p.; Shippen, Joseph (Box 7)
    List of accounts with various officers and men.
  - Statement of accounts due him for horses, 1760 April 20; 1p.; Greer, Andrew (Box 7)
    Lists horses taken into King's service, and amount owed.
  - Return of provisions..., 1760 June 1; 1p.; Graydon, Caleb (Box 7)
    Lists flour, pork, and beef at Fort Augusta.
  - Clothing account for his company, 1760 June 10; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 7)
    Lists men's name, and number and type of article issued.
  - Order to pay James Burd, to Plumstead & Franks, 1760 June 11; 1p. (Box 7)
    Carlisle. Part missing, asking that payment of bill be made.
  - Return of the garrison of Fort Allen, 1760 July 1; 1p. (Box 7)
    Part missing, gives rank and number at Fort.
  - Permit for wagons to pass to Fort Pitt, 1760 July 4; 1p.; Morton, George (Box 7)
    Permission to pass to Fort Pitt with Indian stores.
  - Return of personnel..., 1760 July 7; 1p.; Hunter, Samuel (Box 7)
    Return of men for First Battallion Pennsylvania Regiment.
  - Distribution of horses, 1760 July 9; 1p. (Box 7)
    Lists horses with Col. Mercer's Detachement, and number of horses assigned to each officer.
  - Return of the First Battalion ..., 1760 July 10; 1p. (Box 8)
    Troops at Fort Pitt, and number by rank.
  - Invoice of Thomas Cotter's wagon load ... to Fort Pitt., 1760 July 16; 1p. (Box 8)
    List of items in load, and cost.
  - Invoice of Thomas Cotter's load to Fort Pitt, 1760 July 16; 1p. (Box 8)
    List of items in load, and cost. [different from above list].
  - Return of provisions at Fort Pitt, 1760 July 20; 1p.; Ormsley, John (Box 8)
    Gives return by type of provision.
  - Appraisement of pack horses ..., 1760 July 24; 1p.; Erwin, Robert (Box 8)
    Value of cetain officers horses.
  - List of horses returned from Presqu'Ile, 1760 July 25; 2pp. (Box 8)
    Number of horses returned from certain officers.
  - Account of Dennis McCormick, 1760 July - 1761 September; 1p.; Swan, Hugh (Box 8)
    List of accounting.
  - Appraisal of horses ..., 1760 August 11; 1p.; Erwin, Robert (Box 8)
    Lists name of owner, number of horses, and value.
  - Account of John Mason, a "Batteauxman", 1760 August 27; 1p.; Stephens, Andrew (Box 8)
    Gives dates of service.
  - List of items advanced to John Kennedy of Capt. Price's company, 1760 September; 1p. (Box 8)
    List of clothing items.
  - Appraisement of pack horses, 1760 October 21; 1p.; Erwin, Robert and John Metcalf (Box 8)
    Gives men's name with number, color, brand, and rate for horses.
  - List of recruits at Fort Augusta, 1760 December 26; 1p.; Swan, Hugh (Box 8)
    Lists names of recruits and money paid.
  - Account of rations received of Samuel Hunter, 1761 July; 1p. (Box 8)
    Lists cost of rations received, with miscellaneous accounting at bottom.
  - Account paid to different rolls, 1761 September 13; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 8)
    Lists amounts paid to Pittsburgh, new recruits, Augusta Roll, and cash borrowed.
  - Cash book (accounts paid to various men), 1761 September - October; 9pp.; Burd, James (Box 8)
    Gives name, amount owed, and for what.
  - Return of ordinance and stores at Fort Augusta, 1760 August 1; 1p.; Bard, Peter (Box 8)
    Gives number and type of ordinance.
  - Return of regiment at Presqu'Ile, 1760 September; 1p.; Price, G. (Box 8)
    Return of detachment from Pennsylvania Regiment.
  - Return of coopers at Pittsburgh, 1760 October 7; 1p.; Jameson, David (Box 8)
    Lists men's name, and company.
  - Oath that his horses "gave out" while he was hauling items, 1760 November 11; 1p.; Long, John (Box 8)
    Gives conditions under which the horses "gave out.."
  - Return of provisions at Fort Augusta, 1760 December 1; 1p.; Johnston, Francis (Box 8)
    Lists provisions by type.
  - Roll of Recruits, 1760; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 8)
    Lists names of recruits, and officer recruited by.
  - List of men to be continued at Fort Augusta, 1761 February 21; 1p. (Box 8)
    Lists names of men.
  - Return of boats, etc. at Fort Pitt, 1761 March 14; 1p.; Clapham, William (Box 8)
    Inventories boats and batteaux available.
  - Advertisement of deserter ..., 1761 April 14; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 8)
    Advertisement for John Wood.
  - Statement, 1761 April 22; 4pp.; Burd, James and L. Ourry (Box OS)
    Concerning horses used.
  - Return of a detachment of Pennsylvania force, 1761 May 17; 1p.; Little, John (Box 8)
    Return of men.
  - Return of John Little's Company, 1761 May 27; 1p.; Little, John (Box 8)
    Lists number of men by rank.
  - Return of the garrison at Fort Augusta, 1761 June 1; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 8)
  - Col. Burd's Company's account to Thomas Christy, 1761 June 16; 1p. (Box 8)
    Lists names of men and amount owed. Part of list missing.
  - Report of clothing remaining in his hands, 1761 July 25; 1p.; Folks, Lt. (Box 8)
    Lists number of items on hand.
  - Return of forces at Fort Pitt, 1761 September 18; 1p.; Morgan, Jacob (Box 8)
    Return of Pennsylvania Regiment at Fort Pitt.
  - List of tools sold to James Burd..., 1761 August - October; 1p.; Barrance, James (Box 8)
    Lists date and type of tool sold.
  - Return of the sick, 1761 August 31; 1p.; Milne, James (Box 8)
    Lists company, name of indvidual, and illness.
  - Return of forces at Fort Pitt, 1761 July 26; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 7)
    Return for Pennsylvania Regiment.
  - Weekly return of forces at Fort Pitt, 1761 September 27; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 8)
    Gives return by rank, and occupation.
  - Receipt to James Burd for £21.4.4 for various men, 1761 October 20; 1p.; McClure, John (Box 8)
    Amounts paid for new recruits, listing names and amounts paid.
  - Return of provisions, 1761 November 1; 1p.; Graydon, Caleb (Box 8)
    Accounting of flour, live bullock, and salt at Fort Augusta.
  - Report of bullocks to be slaughtered, 1761 November 6; 1p.; Howell, Reese (Box 8)
    Gives number and location.
  - Account of monies received from various members of Col. Burd's company, 1761 November 8; 1p.; Swan, Hugh (Box 8)
    Lists names of men, money paid, and money received.
  - Report of the bullock guard, 1761 November 15; 1p.; Folk, Jonathan (Box 8)
    Fort Pitt. Report given by officers.
  - Statement of the unfitness of Timothy Innis, 1761 November 19; 1p.; Boyd, Robert (Box 8)
    States Innis is unfit for service, but gives not reason.
  - Memorandum of horses stolen by an Indian., 1761 December 5; 1p.; Bayerley, Mr. (Box 8)
    Bushy Run. Gives descriptions of two horses stolen by an Indian named Mesina. Freeman and Smith 2888.
  - Prices of the clothing, 1761; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 8)
    Lists type of clothing and value.
  - Roll of troops drafted into James Burd's company, 1761; 1p. (Box 8)
    Lists names of recruits.
  - Debts due by Col. Burd's company, 1762 January 19; 1p. (Box 8)
    Lists names of men, and amounts.
  - Receipt to James Burd for rations, 1762 June 7; 1p.; Hunter, Samuel (Box 8)
    For Fort Augusta, gives rations delivered and amount paid.
  - Abstract of rations issued to Fort Augusta, 1762 July; 1p. (Box 8)
    Accounting of rations drawn within certain periods, and by rank.
  - Return of Provisions at Fort Augusta, 1762 September 5; 1p.; Graydon, Caleb (Box 8)
    Lists provisions by type and amount.
  - Certification that sheep strayed..., 1762 October 1; 1p.; Graydon, Caleb (Box 8)
    Notice that seven sheep of Col. Burd's strayed.
  - Memorandum of goods wanted at Fort Augusta, 1762; 1p.; McCormick, Dennis (Box 8)
    Lists items and number needed.
  - Col. Burd's Company, Receipt book [fragmentary], 1762-1764; 20pp. (Box 8)
    Listings for various receipts. Book is in fragmentary condition, some pages are not complete..
  - Provisions account at Fort Augusta, 1762; 1p. (Box 8)
    Lists date of account, with whom, and amount.
  - Abstract of rations issued to Fort Augusta, 1763 February - April; 1p.; Graydon, Caleb (Box 8)
    Gives rations issued for specific periods, and vouchers issued by rank.
  - Return of provisions at Fort Augusta, 1763 October 1; 1p.; Graydon, Caleb (Box 8)
    Lists provisions by type and amount on hand.
  - Memorandum of "Flower" borrowed, 1763 November; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 8)
    Flour borrowed from Robert Barcly.
  - Report of cattle and pots now in use in Col. Burd's Company, 1763 December 6; 1p. (Box 8)
    Lists location and number.
  - Return of pots now inuse..., 1763 December; 1p.; Graydon, Caleb (Box 8)
  - Account of powderhorns, lead, etc. delivered to James Burd..., 1763 July 22; 1p.; Irvine, James (Box 8)
    Lists items and number on hand.
  - Statement of accounts for work on swords for Col. James Burd, 1763 September 21; 1p.; Mullen, John (Box 8)
    Philadelphia. Lists work done, and cost.
  - Account with the Province of Pennsylvania for wagon wheels, wages, etc., 1763 November 5; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 8)
    Lists items received and value.
  - Account of rations..., 1763 November 7; 1p.; Galty, James (Box 8)
    Lists rations issued and cost.
  - List of debts due from Fort Augusta, 1763 November 26; 1p.; Brown, Mary (Box 8)
    Lists person, and amount owed.
  - Caleb Graydon's Company. List of money received, 1763 December 14; 2pp. [bottom missing] (Box 8)
    Gives soldiers' name and amount paid.
  - Account of provisions for James Burd's Company, 1763; 1p.; Galley, James (Box 8)
    List of meat purchased, type and from whom.
  - Abstract of provisions issued at Fort Augusta, 1764; 1p. (Box 8)
    Provies Number of persons and days, time of issue, to whom issued, and total of all rations isued.
  - Return of pots in James Burd's Company, 1764 February 4; 1p. (Box 8)
    Lists number of pots by location.
  - Return of pots belonging to Capt. Greadon's Company, 1764 February 4; 1p. (Box 8)
  - Account with various men at Fort Augusta, 1764 February 22; 2pp.; Burd, James (Box 8)
    Lists name of man, and amount owed.
  - Return of goods in store at Fort Augusta, 1764 March 1; 2pp. [part missing] (Box 8)
  - A return on the different sorts of tools at Fort Augusta..., 1764 April 1; 1p.; Craydon, Caleb (Drawer Oversize)
    Return of tools.
  - Return of provisions at Fort Augusta, 1764 July 1; 1p. (Box 8)
    Lists items, and number.
  - A list of debts due from men in Capt. Caleb Graydon's Company, 1764 July 7; 3pp. (Box 8)
    Lists men's name, and amount due.
  - Promissory note to James Burd, 1764 July 9; 1p.; Beaver, John (Box 8)
    Promise to pay amount, reason not stated.
  - Balance due to the Company, 1764 July 9; 2pp.; Burd, James (Box 8)
    Lists men by rank, with name and amount paid.
  - Promisory note to James Burd, 1764 July 9; 1p.; Thornton, Joseph (Box 8)
    Promis to pay amount, reason not stated.
  - Abstract of provisions issued to Fort Augusta, 1764 July 31; 2pp. [fragment missing] (Box 8)
    Gives number of persons for a given period, where the vouchers were issued, and rations given. Second page has miscellaneous accounting notes.
  - List of sundry debts ... due to Col. Burd, 1764; 2pp.; Graydon, Capt. (Box 8)
    Gives the names of men, and amount owed.
  - Sundry papers sent to Fort Augusta per Mr. Murray, 1764 November 23; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 8)
    Lists certificates and receipts on hand.
  - Statement of accounts from James Burd's Company for stockings, buckles..., 1767 April 5-12; 1p.; Gallespie, Allen (Box 8)
    Receipt for items, and cost.
  - Statement of rations for his men, 1768 September 12; 1p.; Blyth, William (Box 8)
    Lists number and type of rations issued, to whom and when.
  - Longitude and latitude of Ft. Pitt, 1772 November; 3pp.; Smith, William and David Rittenhouse (Box 8)
    Proposal on determining the latitude of Fort Pitt for the purpose of determining the jurisdiction of magistrates in relation to the western boundary of Pennsylvania.
  - Abstract of reports of personnel..., July 1; 1p. (Box 8)
    Gives garrison by rank, and rations issued.
  - Accounts of Col. James Burd's Company with Hugh Swan, n.d.; 1p. (Box 8)
    List of accounts.
  - Account of smith work done at Fort Cumberland for James Burd, 1p. (Box 8)
    Lists work done and cost.
  - Account of rice sent to Fort Augusta, n.d.; 1p.; Boyd, John (Box 8)
    Lists amounts.
  - Accounts, n.d.; 2pp.; Burd, James (Box 8)
    Fragmentary page from an account book.
  - Statement of accounts with James Burd, n.d.; 1p.; Carson, John (Box 8)
    For powder, lead.
  - Journal page from the time of an Indian war, April 2; 2pp. [fragments missing] (Box 8)
    Journal of travels around April 2. No year is given, and parts are missing.
  - List of deserters and servants, 1p.; Burd, James (Box 8)
    Gives names, and status.
  - Commitment order for Sergt. John McCew, n.d.; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 8)
    On suspicion of stealing rum.
  - Inventory of necessaries for smith's work at Fort Augusta, n.d.; 1p. (Box 8)
  - Return of Party Ordered to take ... horses, n.d.; 2pp.; Jameson, David (Box 7)
    Gives account of men not returned, and expenses incurred.
  - Return of men, n.d.; 1p. [Section missing]; Kerr, Jacob (Box 8)
    Give return by rank for Second Battalion.
  - List of carpenter's tools yet wanting, n.d.; 1p. (Box 8)
    Lists tools and number wanted.
  - List of coopers in the Pennsylvania regiment..., n.d.; 1p. (Box 8)
    Lists men by battalion and company.
  - List of meadows within 7 miles of Shippensburg, n.d.; 1p. (Box 8)
    Gives owners name, acres, miles from town, and appraisement.
  - List of men of James Burd's Company whose attestations are lost, or never came to hand., 1p. (Box 8)
    Gives names and date.
  - Muster roll of the company of the command of Lt. Andrew Engell [mutilated], 1p. (Box 8)
    Lists men by name, and gives time of enlistment..
  - Roll of Col. Burd's Company, n.d.; 1p. (Box 8)
    Gives last name of men.
- Personal, 1747-undated; Series IV
  Miscellaneous invoices, receipts, bills of exchange, promissory notes, memoranda relating to Burd's company and his store, including such topics as victualling the troops at Fort Hunter and Fort Augusta, medical care, cutting the road to the Ohio, discipline, ordnance, enlistments, muster rolls, and returns.
  - Meteorological observations, 1747; 2pp. (Box 7, Box 8)
    Observations taken in London.
  - Dimensions for building a ship, 1750; 4pp. (Box 7, Bin 8)
    Dimensions and specifications for building a 260 ton ship.
  - Material for a brewery, n.d.; 1p. (Box 8)
    List of items, and cost.
  - Plan of J.B.'s garden, n.d.; 1p. (Box 8)
    Plan for Burd's garden behind his house in Lancaster.
- Receipts, 1746-1792; Series V; .75 lin. feet
  Receipts to Burd for rents, washing, paint for the Six Nations, portage, glazing, repairs for wagons and boats, fabrics, horses, corn, beans, hay, beer, soap, etc.; receipts for wages, clothing, rum, bounty money, washing, barbering, etc., paid for Burd's company.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1746 March 22; 1p.; Simon, Jacob (Box 8)
    For shoe repair...
  - Shipping receipt to James Burd, 1746 December 31; 1p.; Anderson, William (Box 8)
    Items shipped aboard the Christian of Perth.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1746 Aug 18; 1p.; Westcott, George (Box 8)
    For "All Accounts."
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1747 March 12; 1p.; Wyatt, Mrs. (Box 8)
    For rent in London.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1747 June 4; 1p.; Stirling, Walter (Box 8)
    London. For drafts on various persons.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1747 November 19; 1p.; Goodwin, John (Box 8)
    For making a stable.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1747 December 28; 1p.; Cartringer, John (Box 8)
    For tailoring and material.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1748 February 15; 1p.; Cario, Michall (Box 8)
    For dimond ring.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1748 April 13; 1p.; Goodwin, John (Box 8)
    For making a chest, materials.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1748 May 6; 1p.; Turner, Thomas (Box 8)
    For portage.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1748 June 21; 1p.; Harrison, William (Box 8)
    For posting his books.
  - Receipt to Edward Shippen, 1748 July 4; 1p.; Redmond, Anna (Box 8)
    For the purchase of two sconces.
  - Recipt to James Burd, 1748 July 7; 1p.; Charles & Alexander Stedman (Box 8)
    For £ 105.6.3-3/4.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1748 July 12; 1p.; Charles & Alexander Stedman (Box 8)
    For £30.8.0.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1748 August 26; 1p.; Welsh, Janet (Box 8)
    For rent.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1748 September 15; 1p.; Ronaldson, Nelly (Box 8)
    For washing, etc..
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1748 November 24; 1p.; Hall, David, 1714-1772 (Box 8)
    For dictionary and almanack.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1748 December 15; 1p.; Swan, Daniel (Box 8)
    For payment for making book case.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 January 21; 1p.; McCall, Samuel Jr. (Box 8)
    For purchase of vinegar.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 February 10; 1p.; Carpenter, Thomas (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 February 21; 1p.; Philip, Robert (Box 8)
    For work done on the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 March 22; 1p.; Buchan, Charles (Box 8)
    For board.
  - Receipt to James Burd., 1749 April 5; 1p.; Smith, Jeptha (Box 8)
    For glaising [sic] windows, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 April 29; 1p.; Bridges, Cornelia (Box 8)
    For purchases made.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 April 29; 1p.; Wharton, James (Box 8)
    For £108.17.0.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 May 4; 1p.; Field, Nehemiah (Box 8)
    For freight for a bag of skins.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 May 5; 1p.; Carpenter, Thomas (Box 8)
  - Receipted bill to James Burd, 1749 May (?) 10; 1p.; Jones, Owen (Box 8)
    For flour, bran...
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 June 9; 1p.; Nixon, John (Box 8)
    For rum.
  - Receipt to Jame Burd, 1749 June 19; 1p.; Jones, William (Box 8)
    For "2350 Locust Trinnells."
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 July 15; 1p.; Hill, William (Box 8)
    For £0.11.6.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 July 17; 1p.; Bruce, Alexander (Box 8)
    For knotting.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 July 21; 1p.8; Hall, David, 1714-1772 (Box 8)
    For anchor, nale ...
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 July 31; 1p.; Carter, William (Box 8)
    For the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 August 2; 1p.; Stout, Cornelius, and William Carter (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 August 12; 1p.; Carter, William and Cornelius Stout (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 August 17; 1p.; Satler, Alexander (Box 8)
    For muslin, etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 August 23; 1p.; McCoole, Walter (Box 8)
    For his black horse...
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 September 23; 1p.; Carter, William (Box 8)
    For £20.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 November 8; 1p.; Carpenter, Thomas (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 November 20; 1p.; Sibbald, John (Box 8)
    For wine.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 December 12; 1p.; Wharton, Thomas. (Box 8)
    For gunpowder.
  - Receipt to James burd, 1749 December 21; 1p.; Evans, Simon (Box 8)
    For payment for various jobs.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1749 December 29; 1p.; Evans, Jonathan (Box 8)
    For casks, wine, etc.
  - Receipt, 1749; 1p.; Lindsay, James (Box 8)
    For material for the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 January 4; 1p.; Holt, Samuel (Box 8)
    For riding equipment.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 January 14; 1p.; Ord, John (Box 8)
    For purchase of buttons.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 January 17; 1p.; De Nyce, William (Box 8)
    For stockings etc.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 January 30; 1p.; Molineaux, William (Box 8)
    For items on account.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 February 16; 1p.; Williams, Thomas (Box 8)
    For long boat.
  - Receipt to Robert Philip, 1750 February 28; 1p.; Brad, William (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 February; 3pp.; Lindsay, James (Box 8)
    For supplies for the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 March 5; 1p.; Pinyard, Joseph (Box 8)
    For purchase of beans.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 March 6; 1p.; Burton, Joseph (Box 8)
    For corn, wheat, and pipe staves.
  - Receipt to Philips, 1750 March 6; 1p.; Gibbons, James (Box 8)
    For beans (fragment).
  - Receipt toMr. Philips, 1750 March 7; 1p.; Gibbons, James (Box 8)
    For corn and wheat received aboard the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt, 1750 March 15; 1p.; Gibbons, James (Box 8)
    For corn aboard the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 March 13; 1p.; Wellesay, Robert (Box 8)
    For corn.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 March 15; 1p.; Adams, George (Box 8)
    For wheat.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 March 15; 1p.; Fleeson, Plunket (Box 8)
    For work done, making furniture.
  - Receipt to Capt. Philips, 1750 March 16; 1p.; Rigdon, William (Box 8)
    For painting and guilding the snow, Sally.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 March 17; 1p.; Goforth, Zachariah (Box 8)
    For corn and wheat.
  - Receipt to Robert Philip, 1750 March 23; 1p.; Ellis, Robert (Box 8)
  - Receipt, 1750 March 23; 1p.; Philips, Robert (Box 8)
    For fish-hooks, salt, etc.
  - Receipt to Robert Philip, 1750 March 23; 1p.; Philips, John (Box 8)
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 March 29; 1p.; Wormley, John (Box 8)
    For his father, William Hodge.
  - Receipt to James Burd, 1750 April 21; 1p.; Tyson, Ryner (Box 8)
    For lime.